(Amy:)I can't believe
you've been arrested.
(Sheldon:)I can't believe Penny hasn't.
(Penny:)Sheldon, what did you do?
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm not proud of it,
(Sheldon:)but... I jaywalked.
(Leonard:)Oh, no, it's like
a horror movie.
(Leonard:)We're trapped in a cabin
with a maniac.
(Howard:)I'm surprised
you would do that.
(Sheldon:)No, I crossed
in the middle of the street.
(Sheldon:)And normally, I wouldn't,
(Sheldon:)but I saw an aggressive-looking
Girl Scout,
(Sheldon:)and it was the heart
of cookie season.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, there was
a police officer,
(Sheldon:)and he witnessed
the whole thing.
(Penny:)What... he arrested you for that?
(stammers)
No, he didn't do anything.
(Sheldon:)So I said,
"You just saw me jaywalk.
(Sheldon:)Why aren't you
doing your job?"
(Sheldon:)You know?
"M-Maybe I should arrest you
for-for impersonating
a police officer."
(Penny:)And then you got arrested.
(Sheldon:)Oh, and how.
(Howard:)I feel like I just made
a horrible mistake.
(Bernadette:)Yeah.
(Howard:)But on the other hand,
(Howard:)I didn't kick him
out of our lives.